[
  {
    "Id": "0486bdfa-e8da-42b9-952c-cf54281afc88",
    "Name": "\u6E2C\u8A66",
    "Cards": [
      {
        "Id": "018c5f9e-c0ff-4e0e-8e43-1e4f92f663d9",
        "Front": "test",
        "Back": "\u6E2C\u8A66"
      },
      {
        "Id": "72519949-e653-4aef-95a1-3e8dd30bad2d",
        "Front": "hi",
        "Back": "\u4F60\u597D"
      },
      {
        "Id": "9929bea4-3b4f-4bd1-a285-307e82a8bc7b",
        "Front": "love",
        "Back": "(n.) \u611B(love)\nStrong affection."
      },
      {
        "Id": "c73803d3-23cc-4fce-a930-655243e194bf",
        "Front": "city",
        "Back": "(n.) \u57CE\u5E02\nA large settlement, bigger than a town; sometimes with a specific legal definition, depending on the place."
      },
      {
        "Id": "c8c947ba-eac5-4405-b2df-fdea2bec741c",
        "Front": "cancer",
        "Back": "(n.) \u5DE8\u87F9\u5EA7 06/22 ~ 07/22\nA disease in which the cells of a tissue undergo uncontrolled (and often rapid) proliferation."
      },
      {
        "Id": "e73c0338-d391-4f78-bf3e-11bfcf9afa98",
        "Front": "proliferation",
        "Back": "(n.) \u7E41\nThe process by which an organism produces others of its kind; breeding, propagation, procreation, reproduction."
      },
      {
        "Id": "dda7f32b-62b1-4515-bfc1-9d8615d5acd4",
        "Front": "fine",
        "Back": "(n.) \u7F70\u6B3E; (v.) \u8655\u4EE5\u7F70\u6B3E"
      },
      {
        "Id": "5507db78-b20f-4987-8dc4-8b6ba4b3b917",
        "Front": "pass",
        "Back": "(v.) \u901A\u904E"
      },
      {
        "Id": "42d0ef90-8a07-424f-9c2e-07f5dbb5b31d",
        "Front": "entertainment",
        "Back": "(n.) \u5A1B\u6A02"
      },
      {
        "Id": "3b3b457d-e3cc-4d97-bcf6-c35cc9dc2c02",
        "Front": "enormous",
        "Back": "(adj.) \u5049\u5927\u7684"
      }
    ],
    "ValidCardCount": 10
  }
]